<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Book Club</title>
    <link>https://luminous-daifuku-142c42.netlify.app/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Book Club</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 Mar 2023 15:52:40 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://luminous-daifuku-142c42.netlify.app/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Instagram Scrape</title>
      <link>https://luminous-daifuku-142c42.netlify.app/posts/instagram-scrape/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Mar 2023 15:52:40 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://luminous-daifuku-142c42.netlify.app/posts/instagram-scrape/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Today we will be extracting a list of followers from social media.
While we could do this with web scraping, sometimes it&amp;rsquo;s simply easier to do by using tools specifically made for this. After all, web scraping is all about the output, and less on how you scrape.
Extracting Followers For this demo, we will use Donald Trump&amp;rsquo;s account to extract all of his followers into a spreadsheet.
Specifically, we will be collecting the following data</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Diseases Database (DDB)</title>
      <link>https://luminous-daifuku-142c42.netlify.app/posts/ddb/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Mar 2023 03:29:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://luminous-daifuku-142c42.netlify.app/posts/ddb/</guid>
      <description>Introduction One of the hardest parts of any data science project is gathering good data. Fortunately, many online data repositories exist for us to use!
The Diseases Database (DDB) is one such source. The Diseases Database, developed and maintained by Medical Object Oriented Software Enterprises LTD, is a cross-referenced index of human disease, medications, symptoms, signs, and abnormal investigation findings, intended for medical practitioners and students.
Rather than in hierarchies of anatomical, physiological, or pathological systems, it serves as a way of classifying medical concepts along clinical axes, such as cause/effect, risk factors, interactions, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>S2AND: Allen AI Paper Summary</title>
      <link>https://luminous-daifuku-142c42.netlify.app/posts/s2and/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2023 16:52:30 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://luminous-daifuku-142c42.netlify.app/posts/s2and/</guid>
      <description>Introduction The purpose of this post is to provide readers a quick recap on the S2AND paper by Allen AI. Readers are encouraged to review the original paper for technical details they wish to further investigate. Additionally, Daniel King and Sergey Feldman have done a great job documenting S2AND development in a separate Medium post by Sergey Feldman.
For a post demonstrating the implementation of S2AND, feel free to read the second part of this post.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fourth</title>
      <link>https://luminous-daifuku-142c42.netlify.app/posts/fourth/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Mar 2023 14:39:33 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://luminous-daifuku-142c42.netlify.app/posts/fourth/</guid>
      <description>Introduciton After much time has passed, let&amp;rsquo;s see if I can (1) download this repo (2) create a new file (3) edit the previous files (4) push changes to repo (5) have website update</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Predicting Stocks using a RNN: Part 1</title>
      <link>https://luminous-daifuku-142c42.netlify.app/posts/third/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Aug 2022 15:18:24 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://luminous-daifuku-142c42.netlify.app/posts/third/</guid>
      <description>In this post, I will demonstrate mostly my skills in using the markdown langauge. I will basically try to copy Lil&amp;rsquo;Log&amp;rsquo;s post, and practice with various useful formatting methods like headers, quotes, questions, lists, and the like. I hope you all enjoy!
Overview of Existing Material There are many tutorials online. I particularly like using https://dillinger.io. It&amp;rsquo;s an online editor, and a nice intro to what I can use. Now I will work on creating a list below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Second</title>
      <link>https://luminous-daifuku-142c42.netlify.app/posts/second/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Aug 2022 20:12:11 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://luminous-daifuku-142c42.netlify.app/posts/second/</guid>
      <description>Here is to a new post. Wow, we have already done so much, it&amp;rsquo;s crazy to see how far we&amp;rsquo;ve come to this world. Welp. See you all soon! Bye bye now!
Best, Alejandro</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First</title>
      <link>https://luminous-daifuku-142c42.netlify.app/posts/first/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Aug 2022 20:03:54 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://luminous-daifuku-142c42.netlify.app/posts/first/</guid>
      <description>yeeh yeet. Here we go!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
